<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://math.boskind.tech/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://math.boskind.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://math.boskind.tech/miscStuff/angels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/miscStuff/angels/</guid><description>Angles When did we talk about angles? Lesson1 Lesson1.2</description></item><item><title/><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.14/</guid><description>My classmates said we learned that A transversal is a line the crosses parallel lines&amp;mdash; title: Lesson 14 Alternate Interior Angles Summary Congruent One figure is congruent to another if it can be moved with translations, rotations, and reflections to fit exactly over the other.
When two parallel lines are cut by another line, called a transversal, two pairs of alternate interior angles are created. (“Interior” means on the inside, or between, the two parallel lines.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 1.2</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.2/</guid><description>Lesson 1.2 Unit1 Lesson 2 What did I learn Today? Translation- slides a figure without turning it, Rotation- turns a figure about a point, called the center of rotation, and Reflection- is a transformation representing a flip of a figure.And the figure can go clockwise or counterclockwise. i learned what reflection means/ points on the opposite side of a reflection line the mirror image is a backwards copy of the original figure.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 1.3</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.3/</guid><description>Lesson 1.3 Unit1 Lesson 3
Grid Moves Today we worked with square and isometric (triangle) grids What did I learn today? I learned how to transfer and rotate objects. I learned that if I don&amp;rsquo;t go to school I wont understand math i learned how to use vectors Counterclockwise is left clockwise goes right prime is after a transformation I learned how to use GeoGebra. I learned all of the vocabulary words and what they do.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 1.4</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.4/</guid><description>Unit1 Lesson 4 Making the moves What did I learn today? I learned about translation how you need direction and distance. I learned about reflection and how you need a line of reflection and i learned about rotation and how you need degrees ccw or cc and c.o.r i learned definitions for rotations, translations, rotations and image Vector means direction and distance distence and diretion witch is what the orange dude says the relfected point is called prime that paper hats taped to your shoes can indeed harm people :) I learned about reflection and rotation and what C.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 1.5</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.5/</guid><description>Unit1 Lesson 5 Coordinate Moves Select all of the translations that take Triangle T to Triangle U. There may be more than one correct answer. What did I learn Today? reflecting just remember where to stick the negative sign. (x,-y)x-axs. (-x,y)y axs. when reflecting over y,x axis just find the point and put a - sign. When the x axes is the reflection line y gets - When the y axes is the reflective line gets - We learned that x comes before y in coordinates.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 1.6</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.6/</guid><description>Unit1 Lesson 6 Describing Transformations Andre performs a 90-degree counterclockwise rotation of Polygon P and gets Polygon P’, but he does not say what the center of the rotation is. Can you find the center? What did I learn Today? Unit1Vocab</description></item><item><title>Lesson 1.9</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.9/</guid><description>Moves in Parallel Summary Rigid transformations have the following properties:
A rigid transformation of a line is a line.
A rigid transformation of two parallel lines results in two parallel lines that are the same distance apart as the original two lines.
Sometimes, a rigid transformation takes a line to itself. For example: Unit1Vocab What did I learn today? We learned that blabby gabby and Ranty riley earnt good teachers, and also a new subject.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 10</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.10/</guid><description>Composing Figures Summary Earlier, we learned that if we apply a sequence of rigid transformations to a figure, then corresponding sides have equal length and corresponding angles have equal measure. These facts let us figure out things without having to measure them! What did I learn today? Rotation: # of degrees, C.O.R, direction Reflection: L.O.R Translation: (x + ?, y + ?) rotating something 180 degrees makes it parallel i learned how to macht concrent angels and sides I learned what a parrellogram is wo lines that are equal have little lines on it to show they are equal like three triangles and two of them have some the lines are the same and the angles too.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 11</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.11/</guid><description>What is the same? Summary Congruent One figure is congruent to another if it can be moved with translations, rotations, and reflections to fit exactly over the other.
What did I learn today? That a side ways M means sum I relearned what factorial is after a few years gabys rude because she eases my notes I learned that i really suck at math and tests. I&amp;rsquo;m definitely failing 8th grade i relearned how to find area and perimeter for the 78943026570563rd time :) Congruent shapes have to have the same shape and size and are allowed to flip, move or turn, and angles can be congruent when they are the same size.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 12</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.12/</guid><description>Congruent Polygons Summary Congruent One figure is congruent to another if it can be moved with translations, rotations, and reflections to fit exactly over the other.
What did I learn today? Two figures can still be congruent if they are rotated or have the same type of measurements. To show two figures are congruent, you align one with the other by a sequence of rigid transformations. This is true even for figures with curved sides.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 15</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.15/</guid><description>Adding the Angles in a Triangle Summary What did I learn today? I learned that the insides of a triangle are180 degrees a line that crosses a pair of parallel lines is called a transversal and that all angles have a corresponding angle on the opposite side poooooop in a bucket and mr. boskind is my note caryer I learnd that every thing can and will need to be agnled Alternate interior angles are created when two parallel lines are crossed by another line called a transversal.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 7</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.7/</guid><description>No Bending or Stretching What did I learn Today? we learned what a rigid transformation was When two shqapes or more are the same they call it Congruent. I learned that when reflecting, the y axis doesn&amp;rsquo;t change i learnd more about translate rotate refect Equal = numbers, congruent= triangle abc = triangle a' b' c', Rigid transformation How to spell Scale Factor i learned how to do the units, for a ruler on the board i learned that a inch has 8/8 in it so we can do 1/8 I learned the difference between equal and congruent.</description></item><item><title>Lesson 8</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.8/</guid><description>Rotation Patterns What did I learn today? Any rotation 180 degrees the new line will be parallel. Any 180 degree turn is parallel &amp;lt;3 A 90-degree rotation counter-clockwise is the same as a 270-degree rotation clockwise. when you rotate 180 degrees it dosent matter what way you rotate the lines will be parallel when you rotate a line segment 180 degrees it becomes parallel. congruent is like equal but for shapes I learned that when you rotate a segment 180 degrees, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if its clockwise or counterclockwise because it&amp;rsquo;ll go to the same spot.</description></item><item><title>Lesson1.1</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Lesson1.1/</guid><description>Lesson 1.1 Unit1 Lesson 1 The lesson where Mr. Boskind dances around What did we learn? Today, we recapped on angels and vortexes. We watched some seemingly useless dance turn into a informative recap of angles and counter clockwise and clockwise. We also learned the importance of perseptiveness. Using counter clockwise and clockwise is a more efficient way of telling if the shape turns left or right, drawing a clock over the square is an easy way to tell which way it is turning.</description></item><item><title>Project Stuff</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/miscStuff/projectStuff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/miscStuff/projectStuff/</guid><description>Project stuff Tinkercad Project #1 Create Your Own House with Tinkercad</description></item><item><title>Tinker Cad</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/miscStuff/Tinkercad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/miscStuff/Tinkercad/</guid><description>TinkerCad notes First projectStuff was to create your own house
Tips 2 finger click and drag to change view create a shape that is solid and another shape that is a hole and then group them to get more complex shapes</description></item><item><title>Unit 1</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Unit1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Unit1/</guid><description>Unit 1 Rigid Transforations and Congruence Link to Illustrative Matehmatics - Unit 1 Vocab Lesson 1 Lesson 2 Lesson 3 Lesson 4 Lesson 5 Lesson 6 Lesson 7 Lesson 8 Lesson 9 Lesson 10</description></item><item><title>Unit 1 Vocab</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Unit1Vocab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/Unit1Vocab/</guid><description>Vocab for Unit1 A translation slides a figure without turning it. Every point in the figure goes the same distance in the same direction. For example, Figure A was translated down and to the left, as shown by the arrows. Figure B is a translation of Figure A.
We describe a translation with a vector that we write as (x+?, y+?) A rotation turns a figure about a point, called the center of the rotation.</description></item><item><title>Unit Test Notes</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/UnitTestNotes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit1/UnitTestNotes/</guid><description>Unit 1 TEST Notes I AM REALLY BAD AT MATH KAHOOTS Anything we learned so far Definitions Check out the Unit1Vocab (x+ _ Y+_) that formula All the differnt ways to do a translation Alternate interior angles are created when two parallel lines are crossed by another line called a transversal. Alternate interior angles are inside the parallel lines and on opposite sides of the transversal.</description></item></channel></rss>