<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unit2s on</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/unit2/</link><description>Recent content in Unit2s on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://math.boskind.tech/unit2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dilation</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Dilation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Dilation/</guid><description>Dilation A dilation is a transformation in which each point on a figure moves along a line (Ray) and changes its distance from a fixed point. The fixed point is the center of the dilation. All of the original distances are multiplied by the same scale factor.</description></item><item><title>Equation of a line</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Equation-of-a-Line/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Equation-of-a-Line/</guid><description>Equation of a line The equation of a line is the way that we represent the relationship between x and y of every point on a line. The first form of the equation of a line that we will use is Point Slope Form It is called this because it tells us the Slope of the line and a point on the line. The M in the equation is where we put the Slope of the line The point on the line is shown by (X1, Y1)</description></item><item><title>Slope</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Slope-of-a-line/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Slope-of-a-line/</guid><description>Slope Slope is defined as the steepness, incline, or gradient of a line. It is also defined as the change in y value (&amp;ldquo;rise&amp;rdquo;) over the change in x value (&amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo;). The slope formula is:</description></item><item><title>Student Ideas Unit 2</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Student-Ideas-Unit-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Student-Ideas-Unit-2/</guid><description>Student Ideas Unit 2 I learned what a Slope is congruent means the same shape and size but similar means same shape but different size I learned about rosl (Ratio of Side Lengths) Today we learned a new math word Dilation dilating a shape means scaling it. A ray is a segment that goes in one direction and never ends fall is kinda cold I learned what the center of Dilation is Florida’s really nice :) I should come to school to learn math Today I learned to dilate and perform rigged transformation to prove similarity.</description></item><item><title>Unit 2</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Unit2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Unit2/</guid><description>Unit 2 Illustrative Mathmatics Unit 2 Vocabulary Student Ideas Unit 2 Slope of a line Dilation Equation of a Line</description></item><item><title>Unit 2 Vocab</title><link>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Unit2Vocab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://math.boskind.tech/Unit2/Unit2Vocab/</guid><description>Unit 2 Vocab Unit2 Scale Factor Dilation Center of Dilation Similar Slope of a line The slope of a line is a number we can calculate using any two points on the line. To find the slope, divide the vertical distance between the points by the horizontal distance.
The slope of this line is 2 divided by 3 or 2/3. Simply put, the slope of a line is the ratio of rise to run of a line.</description></item></channel></rss>